Throw it where?
Throw it further back
so if needed I'll throw one and break all his Gloowalls
Get ready to use the Bolt Maker to drop the lightning
Not yet!
Take your time, focus them
Got it
Right after these 10 seconds, use the Bolt Maker to drop the lightning
Drop it now
Alright, Look at launch pad
He's flying straight at us
No matter what, that guy's flying into us
Go left, Alan
Saw him, saw him, breaking it
Breaking this, breaking this
Skyler on the left
One guy on the right, watch right
Alright, I've got eyes on it
Left side, one's low
One knocked
Breaking Moco's gloowall
Confirmed kill
There's still Moco on the left
Breaking this
Clear
Go right